Guide to the Joshua Lederberg Papers SC0186
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1999-141
  - Human Biology 102, 1972-1976
    - Grade sheets (Box 1)
    - Exam files (Box 1)
    - Graded papers (Box 1)
  - Personnel Files, S.U.M.C., 1965-1979
    - Berger, Philip (Box 1)
    - Brutlag, Douglas (Box 1)
    - Gordon, Jo Carol (Box 1)
    - Hamburg, Beatrice (Box 1)
    - Hearn, Donald ReNae (Box 1)
    - Hayflick, Leonard (Box 1)
    - Herzenberg, Leonard (Box 1)
    - Labra, Fernando Flores (Box 1)
    - Grillo, T. A. (Box 1)
    - Holman, Halsted (Box 1)
    - Greene, John R. (Box 1)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2002-022
  - Office Personnel (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Stanford University Faculty Annual Reports/Genetics Department 1962-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - U.S. China Relations: Developments in People’s Republic of China Science and Technology Policy (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - U.S. China Program: J.L.’s Visit (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University: U.S. China Relations Program (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - U.S. China Relations Program – 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - U.S. China Relations Program – 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - U.S. China Relations Program – 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - U.S. China Relations Program – Miscellaneous –1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - U.S. China Relations Program 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - U.S. China Relations Program – 1977 [1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - U.S. China Relations Program – 1977 [2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - U.S. China Relations Program: Lewis Proposal – 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - U.S. China Program: Executive Committee 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - U.S. China Relations Program 11/23/1977: Chinese Delegation on Higher Education (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - U.S. China Relations Program – 1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Arms Control Faculty 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Arms Control Program 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - ACD [Arms Control and Disarmament] Executive Committee 1972-1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - ACD Meeting 9/24/1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Arms Control Japan 1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - ACD Newsletter: 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ACD-Faculty Tutorial 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - ACD Handout 1/15/1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - ACD Report to Ford Foundation 1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - ACD-Japan 1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Arms Control Executive Committee 1975 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Arms Control Faculty 1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - ACD- 1975: Draft Treaty of Environmental Modification (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - ACD Student Papers 1975 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - ACD Miscellaneous 1975 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - ACD Program 1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - ACD Reprints, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - ACD-Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - ACD Group Faculty 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - ACD Japan 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - ACD-Ford Foundation 1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - ACD: Drell lecture 11/10/1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - ACD-138A Course 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - ACD Executive Committee 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - ACD Program 1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - ACD-Institute for Science Policy 1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - ACD-NSF 1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Fourth Interim Report to the Ford Foundation for the Program on Training and Research on Arms Control and Disarmament at Stanford University, March 1, 1977-February 28, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - ACD-1978 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Budgets 1958-1961 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Indirect Departmental Expenses for 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Genetics Lab Equipment (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 701 Welch Road, Suite 1119 (Rental) (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Research Grants (NIH) Research Policy Committee Stanford University 1963 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Research Grants (NSF) Research Policy Committee Stanford University 1963 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - NIH: Funding for the Clinical Sciences Building (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Medical Student Stipends 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Howell, Lillian – Gift 1975 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2002-329
  - Dept. of Genetics, Executive Committee Minutes, 1959-70; 1 microfilm reel (16mm) (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Genetics, Angel R. through Yates [content not verified], 1 microfilm reel (16mm) (Box 1)